Resume

Personal Information

Lee, Yin Ming Calvin

Mobile: (852) 5189 8808

Email: calvinymlee@hotmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

As a graduate in accounting fields, I have acquainted myself with a range of skills that would allow me well organized and able to work independently. Moreover, after gaining few years of working experience, I would like to develop my career in an all-around fund service profession.

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATION

Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting), Curtin University of Technology, Australia

JOB EMPLOYMENT

Aug 2014 - Current

Company: CCB (Asia) Trustee Company Limited

Position: Manager, Custodian Operations & Middle Office

Job description

- Perform security master reference data set up, daily trade bookings and ensure all transactions are processed within internal system in a timely and accurate manner
- Handle daily cash management, including clients' fund transfers, prepare cash projection and forecast reports
- Preparing trade transactions, position and cash reconciliation; Investigate booking discrepancies and reconciliation exceptions.
- Work closely with internal and external counterparts to ensure all reconciliation breaks are resolved
- Prepare trade settlement instructions to sub-custodian; Monitor all settlement transactions closely to avoid any failed trades
- Perform compliance checking on related investment activities and ensure meeting the applicable rules and
- Process and monitor Corporate Actions activities and ensure all instructions are managed and executed promptly and accurately by sub-custodian; Record the relevant CA event details into internal system as well

Performs UAT and new fund master setup by ad hoc basis

• Supervise team of two colleagues; provide training and coaching junior staffs on daily operations

Current salary: HKD 28,350 X 12 months plus bonus

Aug 2013 - Aug 2014

Company: Quality Risk Management & Operations (QRMO)

Position: Operation Analyst

Job description

• Trade booking and allocation on equity, SWAP, FX and future & options etc.

• Communicate with trader, prime broker and executing brokers regarding all trade matters, including trade

settlement, trade give up, trade matching etc.

• Preparing trade transactions, position and cash reconciliation

• Corporate actions process and booking, including stock dividends, stock split, rights, spins off, placement etc.

• Perform Net Asset Value (NAV) estimation and NAV reconciliation for clients

• Prepare risk and exposure report for clients

Current salary: HKD 20,000 X 12 months plus bonus

May 2013 - July 2013

Company: Hedge Fund Operation Ltd (HFO)

Position: Operation Analyst

Job description

• Trade booking and allocation on equity, SWAP, FX and future & options etc.

• Communicate with trader, prime broker and executing brokers regarding all trade matters, including trade

settlement, trade give up, trade matching etc.

• Preparing trade transactions and position reconciliation

Corporate actions process and booking, including stock dividends, stock split, rights, spins off, placement etc.

• Perform Net Asset Value (NAV) estimation for clients

Current salary: HKD 15,000 per month (3 months contract)

April 2011 – April 2013

Company: Principal Trust Company (Asia) Limited

Position: Assistant Officer, Fund Accounting & Valuation Department

Job description

- Calculating Net Asset Value (NAV) for different portfolio, including QDII, SFC and MPF authorized funds
- Updating corporate actions and trades information
- Compliance checking, ensure all portfolio have not breach related rules and regulation
- Preparing cash reconciliation report
- Communicate with brokers regarding price matters
- Preparing QDII trail balance for clients
- Assist in preparing quarter & year-end financial statements
- Performs UAT on programs, which assigned by team head

Current salary: HKD 11,000 X 13 months plus bonus

October 2009 - January 2011

Company: Integrate Electronic Technologies Ltd.

Position: Accounting Assistant

Job description:

- Accounting department support, included daily accounting functions
- Handle accounts receivable & payable
- Preparing month-end closing and year-end financial reports

Salary: HKD 9000 X 12 months plus bonus

SUMMER JOB EMPLOYMENT

March 2009 – August 2009

Company: Coles Supermarket, Australia

Position: Cashier

Job description: In charge on the handling of cash money, general customer services

December 2008 – February 2009

Company: ParaDM Co., Ltd.

Position: Assistant to Director of Finance & Administration

Job description: General administrative, such as data entry, filing & copying, etc.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Fluent Cantonese and English with IELTS test over all 6.5

COMPUTER SKILLS

MS Office, Bloomberg, Geneva, Sophis, Imagine, Omgeo, Multifonds

AVAILABILITY

One months notice

EXPECTED SALARY

Expected: HKD 34,000